Guide to the Elsie H. Hillman Papers, 1920-2015 AIS.2013.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs, c.1930s-2012; XII.
  - Various Political Events, c.1960s-2007; 3.
    - Presidential Inaugural Ball, Elsie Hillman and Bob Dodds, 1969 (Box 102, Folder 38)
    - Presidential Inaugural Ball, Elsie Hillman and Hugh Scott, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 39)
    - Presidential Inauguration Ceremony, Commemorative Photographs, 1981-1989 (Box 102, Folder 40-41)
    - President's Drug Advisory Council Event (Box 102, Folder 42)
    - Pro-Choice Demonstration, Elsie Hillman with Audrey Hillman Fisher and Lilah Fisher, c.1990 (Box 102, Folder 43)
    - Reception for LeRoy S. Zimmerman, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 44)
    - Republican Breakfast Club, Elsie Hillman with Ronald Reagan and John Tabor, 1968 (Box 102, Folder 45-47)
    - Republican Majority for Choice, March for Women's Lives, 2004 (Box 102, Folder 48)
    - Republican Majority for Choice Dinner, c. 2005 (Box 102, Folder 49)
    - Republican National Committee Leadership Conference, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 50)
    - Republican National Committee Mid-Atlantic Conference, 1953 (Box 102, Folder 51)
    - Republican State Committee Party at Hershey Lodge, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Republicans for Choice, Elsie Hillman and Jim Greenwood at rally, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Swearing-in Ceremony of Secretary of Commerce Barbara Franklin, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Community and Charity Events, c.1967-2012; 4.
    Subseries 4 contains photographs involving local community and cultural institutions. This includes events and organizations such as the Hillman Cancer Center, the Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra, and WQED.
    - Carnegie Museum of Natural History, Presentation of Check by Governor Mark Schweiker, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Chatham Center for Women in Politics, Elsie Hillman with Molly Garnett, 1999 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Dinner for David Epperson, 2001 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Gateway Rehab "Hope Has a Home" Gala, 2009 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Heinz Hall Grand Opening, Drue Heinz, Henry, and Elsie Hillman, 1971 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Henry Hillman Hall of Minerals Opening, 1980 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Hillman Cancer Center Dedication, Contact Sheets, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 10-11)
    - Hillman Cancer Center Groundbreaking, 1999 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Historical Society of Western Pennsylvania, Opening Night of the Senator John Heinz History Center, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Institute of Politics, Never a Spectator Event, 2012 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania Breast Cancer Coalition Event, c. 2001 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Persad Auction, Elsie Hillman with Lynn and Charena Swann, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra, Dinner for Anne Patton, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra, Group Photo after Four Singular Sensations Concert, 2007 (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra, Women's Association Annual Fashion Gala, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Pittsburgh Urban Magnet Project, "PUMP 10.0: A Decade of Impact" Event, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Planned Parenthood of Western Pennsylvania 70th Anniversary Celebration, 2000 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - PPG Ice Rink Grand Opening, 2001 (Box 103, Folder 22-24)
    - POW Prayer Day, Elsie Hillman with County Commissioners Tom Foerster, Leonard Staisey, and Bill Hunt, and Pittsburgh religious leaders, 1970 (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - Robert Morris Public Speakers Series, David McCullough with Elsie and Henry Hillman, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 26)
    - Robert Morris Public Speakers Series, Elsie Hillman, Henry Hillman, and Colin Powell, 2006 (Box 103, Folder 27)
    - Save Our Summer '04, 2004 (Box 103, Folder 28-30)
    - Sharing and Caring Boat Ride for Veterans, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - St. Patrick's Day Parade, c. 1967 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Tribute to Billy Conn, Elsie Hillman, Billy and Mary-Louise Conn, 1990 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Tribute to Johnny Costa, 1993 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - University of Pittsburgh Cancer Institute Gala, Ron Herberman, Henry and Elsie Hillman, and Dr. Stanley Marks (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - UPMC Magee Women's Event, Elsie Hillman with Coretta Scott King and Nate Smith, 1999 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - WQED "Dinner with Marvin" Event, 1996 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - WQED Elsie Awards, 2000 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - WQED Elsie Awards, 2002 (Box 104, Folder 9-10)
    - WQED Elsie Awards, 2004 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - WQED Event, Elsie Hillman and Helen Faison, 1975 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - WQED Fundraiser (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - WQED Retirement Party for Lloyd Kaiser and Tom Skinner, 1993 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - WQED TV Auction, 1972 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - WQED TV Auction, 1973 (Box 104, Folder 16-20)
    - WQED TV Auction, 1975 (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - WQED TV Auction, 1978 (Box 104, Folder 22-23)
    - WQED TV Auction, Elsie Hillman and Mime Volunteer (Box 104, Folder 24)
    - WQED TV Auction, John and Teresa Heinz (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - WQED TV Auction, Richard Caliguiri and Elsie Hillman (in gorilla suit) (Box 104, Folder 26)
  - Awards and Ceremonies, 1971-2007; 5.
    Subseries 5 contains photographs of Elsie Hillman and others at award ceremonies or dinners.
    - American Ireland Fund Gala, 2004 (Box 104, Folder 27-29)
    - B'nai Brith, 2003 (Box 104, Folder 30)
    - Chapel of Four Chaplains, Legion of Honor Bronze Medallion Award Dinner, 1999 (Box 104, Folder 31)
    - Chatham College Commencement, 1993 (Box 104, Folder 32)
    - Event Honoring Leonard Staisey, c. 1990s (Box 104, Folder 33)
    - Girl Scouts of Western Pennsylvania, Women and Girls of Distinction Awards, 2007 (Box 104, Folder 34)
    - Hadassah Pittsburgh Chapter Myrtle Wreath Award, 1993 (Box 104, Folder 35)
    - Historical Society of Western Pennsylvania, History Makers Gala, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 36)
    - Historical Society of Western Pennsylvania, History Makers Award, Henry Hillman (Box 104, Folder 37)
    - Jewish National Fund Dinner honoring William Steinburg, 1975 (Box 104, Folder 38)
    - Jewish National Fund, Tree of Life Awards, 2002 (Box 104, Folder 39)
    - National Coalition of Christians and Jews Dinner, 1973 (Box 104, Folder 40)
    - National Flag Foundation, Molly Pitcher Award, 1993 (Box 104, Folder 41)
    - National Friends of Public Broadcasting Event, Elsie Hillman with Elizabeth Campbell, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 42)
    - Pennsylvania Association of Colleges and Universities, Elsie and Henry Hillman receive Sheepskin Award, 2001 (Box 104, Folder 43)
    - Pennsylvania Distinguished Republican Award Dinner, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 44)
    - Pennsylvania Distinguished Republican Awards Dinner for Hugh Scott, 1973 (Box 104, Folder 45)
    - Pennsylvania Society Dinner, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 46)
    - Pittsburgh Courier Top Hat Award, Elsie Hillman and Carl E. Morris, 1971 (Box 104, Folder 47)
    - Pittsburgh Jaycees Community Leader Award, 1978 (Box 104, Folder 48)
    - Pittsburgh Public Theater George S. Kaufmann Awards, Elsie Hillman with Helen Hayes, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 49)
    - Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra Golden Triangle Awards, Elsie Hillman with Rachel Mellon Walton, 2002 (Box 104, Folder 50)
    - Pittsburgh Vectors' Man of the Year Award, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Point Park University Commencement, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - St. Barnabas Hance Awards, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 3-4)
    - Waynesburg University Commencement, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Westminster Choir College Commencement, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Westminster Choir College Commencement, 1991 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Woodrow Wilson Awards, Elsie Hillman, Tom Ridge, Jim Rohr, and Henry Hillman, 2003 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - YWCA Pittsburgh Chapter, Elsie Hillman receiving Allerton Award, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Unidentified Award Dinner, c. 1970s (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Presidents George H. W. Bush, George W. Bush and First Family, 1945-2000; 6.
    Subseries 6 contains photographs of Elsie Hillman with George H.W. and Barbara Bush. All in this subseries are a number of photographs of the Bush family in which Hillman is not included.
    - Air Force Two, Elsie Hillman with Earl Baker, and George H.W. Bush, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Barbara Bush, Pope John Paul II, and George H.W. Bush (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Bus Advertisement of George H.W. Bush, 1993 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Bush Family Photos, 1945-1989 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Duquesne University Commencement, 1981 (Box 105, Folder 15-20)
    - Duquesne University Luncheon, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - Elsie Hillman, Anne Anstine, and George H.W. Bush in Kennebunkport, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - Elsie Hillman, Anne Anstine, and George H.W. Bush at Philadelphia Airport, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 23)
    - Elsie Hillman and Barbara Bush, 1987-1991 (Box 105, Folder 24-27)
    - Elsie Hillman, Barbara and George H.W. Bush, 1979 (Box 105, Folder 28)
    - Elsie Hillman, Barbara and George H.W. Bush, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 29)
    - Elsie Hillman, Barbara and George H.W. Bush, and Earl Baker, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 30)
    - Elsie Hillman and George H.W. Bush, 1979-1992 (Box 105, Folder 31-41)
    - Elsie Hillman, George H.W. Bush, Theresa and Robert D'Angelis, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 42)
    - Elsie Hillman, George H.W. Bush, and Tom Ridge, c.1993-1994 (Box 105, Folder 43)
    - Elsie Hillman, George H.W. Bush, and Charlie Sexton, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 44)
    - Elsie Hillman, George H.W. Bush, and Jay Waldman, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 45)
    - Elsie Hillman, George W. Bush, Tom Ridge, and Unknown, c. 2000 (Box 105, Folder 46)
    - Elsie and Henry Hillman with George H.W. Bush, 1987 - c. 2000 (Box 105, Folder 47-50)
    - Elsie and Henry Hillman with George H.W. and Barbara Bush, c. 1980s (Box 105, Folder 51)
    - Elsie and Henry Hillman with George W. Bush, c. 1992 (Box 105, Folder 52)
    - Elsie and Henry Hillman with George W. Bush and Tom Ridge, c. 2000 (Box 105, Folder 53)
    - Elsie and Henry Hillman with Jim Roddey, Audrey Hillman Fisher, and George W. Bush (Box 105, Folder 54)
    - Elsie Hillman greeting George H.W. Bush at Greater Pittsburgh Airport, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 55)
    - Elise Hillman greeting George H.W. Bush at Norristown Airport, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 56)
    - Elsie Hillman greeting George H.W. Bush, Arlen Specter, and Larry Coughlin at Philadelphia Airport, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 57-58)
    - Event hosted by Douglas Danforth, c. 1988-1992 (Box 105, Folder 59)
    - Extra Mile Foundation Visit, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 60)
    - Fundraiser for Arlen Specter, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 61)
    - George H.W. Bush, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 62)
    - George H.W. Bush, c. 1980s (Box 105, Folder 63)
    - George H.W. and Barbara Bush, c. 1980s-1990s (Box 106, Folder 1-5)
    - George H.W. Bush and Mikhail Gorbachev, c. 1980s (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Henry Hillman and George H.W. Bush, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Millie the White House Dog, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Operation Desert Storm Commemorative Photograph, 1991 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania Bush Volunteer Day, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 10-12)
    - State Visit of Boris Yeltsin, 1992 (Box 106, Folder 13-14)
    - Walker's Point (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - White House Exhibit, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 16-17)
    - White House Restoration Fund Reception, Elsie Hillman, David Rockefeller, and Barbara Bush, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 18)
    - Yacht Madcap, 1988 (Box 106, Folder 19-23)
  - Presidential Photographs, 1960-c.1990s; 7.
    Subseries 7 contains photographs of U.S. Presidents pictured with Elsie and Henry Hillman, in addition to these photographs there are a handful of Presidential portraits.
    - Carter, Henry Hillman with Jimmy Carter, c. 1970s (Box 106, Folder 24)
    - Eisenhower, Elsie Hillman and Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 25)
    - Ford, Elsie Hillman, Marion Bell, and Gerald Ford, c. 1974 (Box 106, Folder 26)
    - Ford, Elsie Hillman, Marion Bell, Gerald Ford, and Richard Schweiker, c. 1974 (Box 106, Folder 27)
    - Ford, Elsie Hillman, Gerald Ford, and Cecily Grant (Box 106, Folder 28)
    - Ford, Elsie and Henry Hillman with Gerald Ford, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 29)
    - Ford, Elsie and Henry Hillman, Jack Heinz, Gerald Ford, Teresa and H. John Heinz III (Box 106, Folder 30)
    - Ford, Elsie Hillman, John Woznisky, and Gerald Ford, 1976 (Box 106, Folder 31)
    - Ford, Portrait of Gerald R. Ford (Box 106, Folder 32)
    - Nixon, Elsie Hillman and Richard Nixon, 1969 (Box 106, Folder 33)
    - Nixon, Elsie Hillman, Milner Roberts, and Richard Nixon, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 34)
    - Nixon, Elsie Hillman with Richard Scaife, Ed Howard, John Rawlins, and Richard Nixon, 1971 (Box 106, Folder 35)
    - Reagan, Elsie Hillman and Ronald Reagan, 1988 (Box 106, Folder 36)
    - Reagan, Elsie Hillman, Arlen Specter, and Ronald Reagan (Box 106, Folder 37)
    - Reagan, Portraits of Ronald Reagan (Box 106, Folder 38-39)
    - Republican Senatorial Inner Circle, Gerald and Betty Ford, Ronald and Nancy Reagan, Richard and Patricia Nixon, and George H.W. and Barbara Bush, c. 1990s (Box 106, Folder 40)
  - Elsie Hillman and Hillman Family, c.1920s-2005; 8.
    Subseries 8 contains photographs of Elsie Hillman as well as relatives and family members of Hillman.
    - Audrey Hilliard (Sister-in-Law), c. 2000s (Box 106, Folder 41)
    - Elsie Hillman, c. 1920s-1940s (Box 106, Folder 42)
    - Elsie Hillman, c. 1960s (Box 106, Folder 43)
    - Elsie Hillman, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 44)
    - Elsie Hillman, c. 2000s (Box 106, Folder 45)
    - Elsie Hillman (in fur coat), c. 1960s (Box 106, Folder 46)
    - Elsie Hillman (wearing Bush shirt), c. 1988 (Box 106, Folder 47)
    - Elsie Hillman speaking at William Penn Hotel, c. 1960s (Box 106, Folder 48)
    - Elsie Hillman viewing drawing of Governor Raymond Shafer, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 49)
    - Elsie and Henry Hillman, c. 1950s (Box 106, Folder 50)
    - Elsie and Henry Hillman, 1976 (Box 106, Folder 51)
    - Elsie and Henry Hillman, c. 1970s (Box 106, Folder 52)
    - Elsie and Henry Hillman, c. 2000s (Box 106, Folder 53)
    - Elsie and Henry Hillman, at Birthday Party for Drue Heinz, 2000 (Box 106, Folder 54)
    - Group Photograph of Hillman family outside of Hillman Cancer Center, c. 2000s (Box 106, Folder 55)
    - Henry L. Hillman (Box 106, Folder 56)
    - Henry L. Hillman (at industrial site), c. 1950s (Box 106, Folder 57)
    - Henry L. Hillman, Historical Society of Western Pennsylvania History Makers Award (Box 106, Folder 58)
    - Henry Hillman Jr, 1988 (Box 106, Folder 59)
    - Juliet Lea Hillman, Bill Hillman, Henry Hillman Jr., and Audrey Hillman (Box 106, Folder 60)
    - Wedding Reenactment, 2005 (Box 106, Folder 61)
  - Group Photographs including Elsie Hillman, c.1948-2012; 9.
    Subseries 9 contains photographs of Elsie Hillman featured with various individuals and is arranged primarily by last name.
    - John E. Angle and David Roderick (Box 106, Folder 62)
    - Anne Anstine and Marlene Carrier, 1992 (Box 106, Folder 63)
    - Anne Anstine and Unknown (Box 106, Folder 64)
    - Lee Atwater (Box 106, Folder 65)
    - Rev. John Baiz, 1965 (Box 106, Folder 66)
    - Dexter Baker (Box 106, Folder 67)
    - Jim Baker and Henry Hillman (Box 106, Folder 68)
    - Hank Beukema, 1992 (Box 106, Folder 69)
    - Ray Bliss, Charles Percy, and Norbert T. Tiemann, 1967 (Box 106, Folder 70)
    - Victor Borge, c. 1948 (Box 106, Folder 71)
    - Bill Burns (Box 106, Folder 72)
    - Frick Byers, Jim Fulton, Hugh Scott, Marion Bell, and Marion Scott (Box 106, Folder 73)
    - Dick Caliguiri and John Bonassi (Box 106, Folder 74)
    - "'Chink' and his friend", 1980 (Box 106, Folder 75)
    - John Connally, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 76)
    - Johnny Costa (Box 106, Folder 77)
    - Arthur Edmunds (Box 106, Folder 78)
    - Dick Frame, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 79)
    - Bob Friend and Bill Hunt (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Jim Fulton and Marion Metro (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Jim Fulton and Unknown (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Andy Gleason, George Bloom, Ted Rubino, Frank Pasquerilla, Bill Scranton, and Hugh Scott (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Jack Heinz (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Henry Hillman (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Henry Hillman, Dick Cheney, and Tom Ridge (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Henry Hillman and Ron Herberman, c. 1996 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Henry Hillman and Lorin Maazel (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Henry Hillman, Sophie Masloff, Rita Wilson Kane, and Unknown (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Henry Hillman and George Miles (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Henry Hillman and Tom Ridge, c. 2000 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Bill Hunt and Bob Duggan (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Jack Jordan (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Nancy Landon Kasselbaum, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Ron Kaufman (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - Joe Laquatra (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - Charles Lieberth (Box 107, Folder 18-19)
    - Barbara Love, Ray Primas, "Teenie Harris", Ken Love, and Barbara Primas, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 20)
    - Revered Arthur McAnulty (Box 107, Folder 21)
    - George Miles (Box 107, Folder 22)
    - Tom Murphy, and Joe Laquatra (Box 107, Folder 23)
    - Queen Noor of Jordan, 2005 (Box 107, Folder 24)
    - Sheldon Parker (Box 107, Folder 25)
    - Thomas Petrone, 1999 (Box 107, Folder 26)
    - Morgan Plant, John Denny, Gordon Woodrow, Steve Dunkle, Pat Saylor, and Bob Colonna, 2012 (Box 107, Folder 27)
    - Johno Prascak, 2007 (Box 107, Folder 28)
    - Maureen Reagan, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 29)
    - Nancy Reagan, 1986 (Box 107, Folder 30)
    - Condoleeza Rice, 2004 (Box 107, Folder 31)
    - Cokie Roberts, George Miles, and Claudette Lewis, 2004 (Box 107, Folder 32)
    - Nelson Rockefeller, Jack Heinz, and Richard Thornburgh, c. 1968 (Box 107, Folder 33)
    - Nelson Rockefeller and Martha Bell Schoeninger, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 34)
    - Nelson Rockefeller, Hugh Scott, Marion Scott, and Dick Frame, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 35)
    - Jim Roddey, c. 1999 (Box 107, Folder 36-37)
    - Jonas Salk and Richard Thornburgh (Box 107, Folder 38)
    - Martha Bell Schoeninger, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 39)
    - Bill Scranton III, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 40)
    - Bill Scranton III, Ginnie and Richard Thornburgh, c. 1978 (Box 107, Folder 41)
    - Bob Shirey, Shirley Collins, and Howard Baker, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 42)
    - Nate Smith (Box 107, Folder 43)
    - Arlen Specter, Dan Quayle, and Henry Hillman (Box 107, Folder 44)
    - William Steinberg and Wesley Posvar, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 45)
    - Louis W. Sullivan, c. 1990s (Box 107, Folder 46)
    - Richard Thornburgh, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 47)
    - Richard Thornburgh (Box 107, Folder 48)
    - Julie Uram, c. 1996 (Box 107, Folder 49)
    - Eddie Waldron and Unknown, 1967 (Box 107, Folder 50)
    - Andrew Young, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 51)
    - Campaign Office Workers, c. 1992 (Box 107, Folder 52)
    - Unknown, c. 1970s (Box 107, Folder 53)
  - Group Photographs not including Elsie Hillman, c.1944-c.2000s; 10.
    Subseries 10 contains group photographs in which Elsie Hillman is not pictured.
    - Walter Curley, c. 1944 (Box 107, Folder 54)
    - Walter Curley and John Lindsay (Box 107, Folder 55)
    - D. Michael Fisher and John Denny, c. 2000s (Box 107, Folder 56)
    - Drue and Jack Heinz (Box 107, Folder 57)
    - H. John Heinz III (Box 107, Folder 58)
    - H. John Heinz III and Teresa Heinz, 1971 (Box 107, Folder 59)
    - Vira Heinz, Jim Walton, and Henry Hillman (Box 107, Folder 60)
    - Juliet Lea Hillman, Nelson Rockefeller, Henry Hillman Jr, and Hugh Scott (Box 107, Folder 61)
    - Harry Markowitz and Bob Duggan (Box 107, Folder 62)
    - Harry Markowitz and William W. Scranton Jr. (Box 107, Folder 63)
    - Richard Thornburgh and Robert Duggan, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 64)
    - Richard Thornburgh and Joe Durzo, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 65)
  - Portraits and Publicity Photographs, 1960s-1990s; 11.
    Subseries 11 contains portraits and publicity photos of individuals.
    - Anne Anstine (Box 107, Folder 66)
    - Lee Atwater (Box 107, Folder 67)
    - Victor Borge (Box 107, Folder 68)
    - Drue Heinz (Box 107, Folder 69)
    - Jesse Helms, 1986 (Box 107, Folder 70)
    - Ron Herberman, c. 1995 (Box 107, Folder 71)
    - Herman LaMark (Box 107, Folder 72)
    - Tom Ridge, c. 1980s (Box 107, Folder 73)
    - Nelson Rockefeller, c. 1970s (Box 107, Folder 74)
    - Hugh Scott (Box 107, Folder 75)
    - John K. Tabor, c. 1960s (Box 107, Folder 76)
  - Other, 1967-2000s; 12.
    Subseries 12 contains photographs, negatives, and cartoons used or sent to Elsie Hillman.
    - Allegheny Republican Party Candidates depicted as babies, 1967 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Blair House, c. 1980s (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Board of Campaign Buttons (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Calvary Episcopal Church, Photographs from Development Campaign Book, 1971 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Carnegie Cup, Photograph submitted to Heinz Memorial Committee (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Cartoon depicting George Bloom (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Hungerford, Cy, Cartoons depicting Elsie Hillman as Allegheny County Republican Chairwoman, 1967-1971 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Negatives (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Republican Party Cartoon (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - UPMC Employees, Press photographs, 2000s (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Photo Albums and Scrapbooks, 1960s-1997; 13.
    Subseries 13 contains photo albums and scrapbooks given to Hillman.
    - Photo Album, Zonta International "Tea with Elsie Hillman", 1997 (Box 108, Volume 1)
    - Scrapbook 1 (Box 109, Volume 1)
    - Scrapbook 2 (Box 109, Volume 2)
    - Scrapbook 3 (Box 109, Volume 3)
  - Oversized Images and Cartoons, 1967-2006; 14.
    Subseries 14 contains oversized images and cartoons. These include a number of enlarged photographs as well as cartoons by Cy Hungerford drawn to commemorate Elsie Hillman's role as Allegheny County Republican Chair.
    - Gerald Ford (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Elsie Hillman, Barbara Bush and Sophie Masloff, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Elsie Hillman, George H.W. and Barbara Bush, and Esther Curley, c. 1980s (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Elsie Hillman and Gerald Ford (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Elsie Hillman and Nelson Rockefeller, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Elsie Hillman, Nelson Rockefeller, George Bloom, Hugh and Marion Scott, and Dick Frame, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Elsie Hillman, Nelson Rockefeller, Edward Speer and his wife (unnamed), 1968 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Elsie Hillman with Political Supporters, 1980 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - William W. Scranton Jr. (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Ray Shaffer (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - National Republican Senatorial Committee, Group Photograph (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - White House Christmas Reception, Elsie Hillman and Barbara Bush, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Ray Bliss (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Cartoon of Hugh Scott (as William Penn) (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Election Day Newspapers, 1971 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Elsie and Henry Hillman with George H.W. and Barbara Bush, c. 1980s (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Hungerford, Cy, Cartoon commemorating Elsie Hillman's election as County Republican Chairwoman, 1967 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Hungerford, Cy, Cartoon commemorating Elsie Hillman reacting to Democratic landslide (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Hungerford, Cy, Cartoon commemorating Elsie Hillman's retirement as Allegheny County Republican Chairwoman, 1970 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Northside Urban Pathways Charter School Event (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Parson, A., Cartoon depicting Elsie Hillman as a nurse (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh Rotary Club, Drawing of Elsie Hillman, 1990 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Presidential Election Newspapers, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Republican Senatorial Inner Circle, c. 1980s (Box 111, Folder 12)